Guide to the Residential College Seminar Program, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Residential College Seminar Program records, 1969-1993; Accession 1999-A-091
  - Bilingsley CSDC 239b (Box 28, Folder 1416)
  - Barbara Harmel CSDC/ CSJE 262b (Box 28, Folder 1417)
  - LambCSBR 161A (Box 28, Folder 1418)
  - Linda Safran CSDC/ CSCM 258b (Box 28, Folder 1419)
  - Davidf. Muste & Robert Byck CSDC/ CSPC 264b (Box 28, Folder 1420)
  - Muste CSPC/ CSDC 238b (Box 28, Folder 1421)
  - Timothy Dwight: Budgets & Costs 1984 (Box 28, Folder 1422)
  - Kumbale N. Nayak CSTD/ CSTC 263b (Box 28, Folder 1423)
  - Nayak CSBK 105A (Box 28, Folder 1424)
  - Barbara Harlow CSTD/ CSES 260b (Box 28, Folder 1425)
  - Marion S. Adelberg CSTD/ CSBR 265b (Box 28, Folder 1426)
  - Michael T. Harrigann CSTD/ CSTC 262b (Box 28, Folder 1427)
  - Harrigan CSTD 163b (Box 28, Folder 1428)
  - Harrigan CSTD 217b (Box 28, Folder 1429)
  - Harrigan CSCC 123b (Box 28, Folder 1430)
  - Jonathan Edwards: Budgets & Costs: 1984 (Box 28, Folder 1431)
  - Teresa E. M. Carballal CSJE/ CSMC 259b (Box 28, Folder 1432)
  - Judy Chung- wa Ho CSJE/ CSTC 258b (Box 28, Folder 1433)
  - Maggie Scarf CSJE 260b (Box 28, Folder 1434)
  - Scarf CSJE 191b (Box 28, Folder 1435)
  - Scarf CSJE 155a (Box 28, Folder 1436)
  - Carlos H. Salguero CSMC 265b (Box 28, Folder 1437)
  - Asger Aaboe CSMC 262b (Box 28, Folder 1438)
  - Donald R. DeLuca CSMC/ CSBK 266b (Box 28, Folder 1439)
  - Morse: Budgets & Costs 1984 (Box 28, Folder 1440)
  - Sarah Deutsch CSBK/ CSMC 74A (Box 28, Folder 1441)
  - Thomas Y. Levin CSBK/ CSMC 270A (Box 28, Folder 1442)
  - Thomas Y. Levin CSBK/ CSMC 270A (Box 28, Folder 1443)
  - Gregory M. Herek CSBR/ CSES 270A (Box 28, Folder 1444)
  - Kane Paula, M. CSBR/ TD 271A (Box 28, Folder 1445)
  - Carmel Shaw CSBR/ CSJE 272A (Box 28, Folder 1446)
  - Fred Streibeigh CSBR 275A (Box 28, Folder 1447)
  - Robert M. Baum CSCC/ CSBK 271A (Box 28, Folder 1448)
  - Baum CSTD 166b/ CSMC 166b (Box 28, Folder 1449)
  - Baum CSTD/ CSCC 180A (Box 28, Folder 1450)
  - David Melchinger CSCC 273A (Box 28, Folder 1451)
  - Ken Frieden CSDC/ CC272A (Box 28, Folder 1453)
  - David Kahn CSDC 271A (Box 28, Folder 1454)
  - Robert Massie CSDC/ CSMC 277A (Box 28, Folder 1455)
  - John A. McKesson CSTD/ CSTC 275A (Box 29, Folder 1456)
  - Susan Rabiner CSTD/ CSBR 274A (Box 29, Folder 1457)
  - Rabiner CSBR/ CSTD 250A (Box 29, Folder 1458)
  - Paul Rosenblatt & Jennifer Sage CSTD/ CSES 272A (Box 29, Folder 1459)
  - Sage/ Rosenblatt CSTD/ CSBR 236b (Box 29, Folder 1460)
  - Brad Westerfield CSTD 270A (Box 29, Folder 1461)
  - Selesky CSTD/ CSBK 176b (Box 29, Folder 1462)
  - Selesky CSSY/ CSCC 230A (Box 29, Folder 1463)
  - Selesky CSSY 193b (Box 29, Folder 1464)
  - Howard J. Brown CSJE/ CSCC 276A (Box 29, Folder 1465)
  - Janus Varga CSJE/ CSSY 278A (Box 29, Folder 1466)
  - Varga CSJE/ CSSM 245b (Box 29, Folder 1467)
  - Davis Apter CSMC/ CSJE 271A (Box 29, Folder 1468)
  - Apter CSMC/ CSJE 228A (Box 29, Folder 1469)
  - Peter Hauslohner CSMC 276A (Box 29, Folder 1470)
  - Thomas Christensen CSPC/ CSTC 272A (Box 29, Folder 1471)
  - Neil Frank Lazarus CSPC/ CSSM 275A (Box 29, Folder 1472)
  - Lazarus CSBK 238b (Box 29, Folder 1473)
  - Lazarus CSJE 23b (Box 29, Folder 1474)
  - Jan Albers CSSY/ CSSM 273A (Box 29, Folder 1475)
  - Roderick Jensen CSSM/ 270A (Box 29, Folder 1476)
  - Jensen CSSM 217b (Box 29, Folder 1477)
  - Candace Waid CSSM/ SY 271A (Box 29, Folder 1478)
  - Virginia Anne Bonito CSES/ CSTC 271A (Box 29, Folder 1479)
  - Kenneth Myers CSTC/ CSSY 274A (Box 29, Folder 1480)
  - Myers CSMC 193b (Box 29, Folder 1481)
  - Kim Powers CSTC/ CSSM 276A (Box 29, Folder 1482)
  - Trumull Expense Reports 1984- 1985 (Box 29, Folder 1483)
  - Migiel CSTC 283b (Box 29, Folder 1484)
  - Odendahl CSES/ CSDC 282b (Box 29, Folder 1485)
  - Sledge CSES 278b (Box 29, Folder 1486)
  - Volk CSES 280b1985 (Box 29, Folder 1487)
  - Ezra Stiles Budgets & Costs 1985 (Box 29, Folder 1488)
  - Bollard CSSM 281b (Box 29, Folder 1489)
  - Fitzpatrick CSSM/CSTD 279b (Box 29, Folder 1490)
  - Paine CSSM/ CSBK 282b (Box 29, Folder 1491)
  - Silliman Expense Reports 1985 (Box 29, Folder 1492)
  - Saybrook Expense Reports 1985 (Box 29, Folder 1493)
  - Gariepy CSSY/ CSBR 282b (Box 29, Folder 1494)
  - Gariepy/ Marban CSSY/ CSBK 137A (Box 29, Folder 1495)
  - Gariepy/ Marban CSSY104A (Box 29, Folder 1496)
  - Rubenstein CSCC/ CSSY 279b (Box 29, Folder 1497)
  - Pierson Expense Reports 1985 (Box 29, Folder 1498)
  - Engleman & Wyman CSPC/ CSCC 281b (Box 29, Folder 1499)
  - Gitlin CSPC/ CSCC 282b (Box 29, Folder 1500)
  - Jay Gitlin CSPC 259b (Box 29, Folder 1501)
  - Manning CSPC/ CSSM 277b (Box 29, Folder 1502)
  - Morrissey CSPC/ CSES 279b (Box 29, Folder 1503)
  - Morse Expense Reports 1985 (Box 29, Folder 1504)
  - Kalabinski CSMC/ CSJE 283b (Box 29, Folder 1505)
  - Kalabinski, Jacek M. CSMC/ CSJE 264b (Box 29, Folder 1506)
  - Best CSJE 282b (Box 29, Folder 1507)
  - Gordon CSJE/ CSMC 279b (Box 29, Folder 1508)
  - Sichel CSJE/ CSMC 280b (Box 29, Folder 1509)
  - Jonathan Edwards Expense Reports 1985 (Box 29, Folder 1510)
  - Davenport Expense Reports 1985 (Box 30, Folder 1511)
  - Timothy Dwight Expense Reports 1985 (Box 30, Folder 1512)
  - Silva CSMC/ CSSM 250A (Box 30, Folder 1513)
  - Simpson CSCC 285b (Box 30, Folder 1514)
  - Calhoun Budgets & Costs 1985 (Box 30, Folder 1515)
  - Lamm CSBR 285b (Box 30, Folder 1516)
  - Lamm CSPC 163b (Box 30, Folder 1517)
  - Arneson CSBR/ CSCC 278b (Box 30, Folder 1518)
  - Atlas CSBR/ CSES 277b (Box 30, Folder 1519)
  - Atlas CSES/ CSTC 240b (Box 30, Folder 1520)
  - Atlas CSJE/ CSPC 205A (Box 30, Folder 1521)
  - Lhermitte CSBR/ CSES 286b (Box 30, Folder 1522)
  - Branford Expense Reports 1985 (Box 30, Folder 1523)
  - Berkeley Expense Reports 1985 (Box 30, Folder 1524)
  - Swensen CSBK/ CSSY 283b (Box 30, Folder 1525)
  - Swensen, David Frederick CSSY/ CSBk 262b (Box 30, Folder 1526)
  - Swensen CSBK/ CSSY 195b (Box 30, Folder 1527)
  - Swensen CSBK 211A (Box 30, Folder 1528)
  - Dreyfus CSBK/ CSES/ CSDC 281b (Box 30, Folder 1529)
  - Pierce CSBK 280b (Box 30, Folder 1530)
  - Shaw CSBK/ CSMC 285b (Box 30, Folder 1531)
  - John A. Shaw CSBK/ CSCC 265b (Box 30, Folder 1532)
  - Residential College SeminarListings (no Manilla Folder) 1984 & 1985 (Box 30, Folder 1533)
  - CTRC Agenda & Minutes 1984- 1985 (Box 30, Folder 1534)
  - CTRC Agenda & Minutes 1985- 1986 (Box 30, Folder 1535)
  - Berkeley College: Expenses & Costs 1986 (Box 30, Folder 1536)
  - Branford College: Expenses & Costs 1986 (Box 30, Folder 1537)
  - Osborne, David E. CSBR 290A (Box 30, Folder 1538)
  - Gornick, Lisa CSBR/ CSTD 289A (Box 30, Folder 1539)
  - Calhoun College: Expenses & Costs 1986 (Box 30, Folder 1540)
  - Gussow, Alan CSCC/ CSES 287A 1985 (Box 30, Folder 1541)
  - Lant Antonia CSCC/ CSSY 290A (Box 30, Folder 1542)
  - Millard, Peter & Matthews, Sharon CSCC/ CSSY 292A (Box 30, Folder 1543)
  - Owen, Wendy CSCC/ CSSY 288b (Box 30, Folder 1544)
  - Owen CSSM/ CSCC 280b (Box 30, Folder 1545)
  - Owen CSSM/ CSDC 249A 1983 (Box 30, Folder 1546)
  - Davenport College: Expenses & Costs 1986 (Box 30, Folder 1547)
  - Shain, Barry CSDC/ CSSY 289A (Box 30, Folder 1548)
  - Shain CSES/ CSDC 283b (Box 30, Folder 1549)
  - Letwin CSDC/ CSTD 280b (Box 30, Folder 1550)
  - Timothy Dwight: Budgets & Costs 1986 (Box 31, Folder 1551)
  - Jonathan Edwards: Budgets & Costs 1986 (Box 31, Folder 1552)
  - Engle, Lars CSJE 290A (Box 31, Folder 1553)
  - Murray CSSY/ CSTD 253A 1983 (Box 31, Folder 1555)
  - Murray SY/ BK 54A (Box 31, Folder 1556)
  - Hearne, Vicki CSTD/ CSCC 302b (Box 31, Folder 1557)
  - Butler, Judith CSTD/ CSBK 292b (Box 31, Folder 1558)
  - Lawrance, Simon CSJE/ CSES 296b (Box 31, Folder 1559)
  - Echart, Kevin CSJE? CSES 289A (Box 31, Folder 1560)
  - Whiteman, Harold CSJE 291A (Box 31, Folder 1561)
  - Whiteman, Harold Jr. CSJE 273A (Box 31, Folder 1562)
  - Chehabi, Houchang CSJE/ CSSY 299b (Box 31, Folder 1563)
  - Chehabi CSJE/ CSSY 281b (Box 31, Folder 1564)
  - Chehabi CSTD/ CSMC 191b (Box 31, Folder 1565)
  - Engle, Lars CSJE 290b (Box 31, Folder 1566)
  - Zwarg, Christina CSBR/ CSDC 295b (Box 31, Folder 1567)
  - Whiting, Cecile CSDC/ CSTD 293b1986 (Box 31, Folder 1568)
  - Chernoff, Fred CSDC/ CSBR 300b (Box 31, Folder 1569)
  - Godfrey, John CSCC 303b (Box 31, Folder 1570)
  - Morse College: Budgets & Expenses 1985- 1986 (Box 31, Folder 1571)
  - Baron, Larry CSMC 291A (Box 31, Folder 1572)
  - Engler, Michael CSMC. CSBK 287A (Box 31, Folder 1573)
  - Engler, Michael CSMC/ CSTC 256b (Box 31, Folder 1574)
  - Pierson College: Budgets & Costs 1986 (Box 31, Folder 1576)
  - Doughty, Robert A. CSPC287A (Box 31, Folder 1577)
  - Doughty CSPC/ CSES 249A 1983 (Box 31, Folder 1578)
  - Doughty CSPC 226A (Box 31, Folder 1579)
  - Manganyi, Noel Chabani CSPC 288A (Box 31, Folder 1580)
  - Saybrook College: Budgets & Costs (Box 31, Folder 1581)
  - Cummings, Scott CSSY/ CSDC 291A (Box 31, Folder 1582)
  - Dittes, James CSSY/ CSCC 294A (Box 31, Folder 1583)
  - Starr, John Bryan CSSY/ CSPC 286A (Box 31, Folder 1584)
  - Starr CSPC 171b (Box 31, Folder 1585)
  - Woo CSTC/ CSMC 282b (Box 31, Folder 1586)
  - Silliman College: Budgets & Costs (Box 31, Folder 1587)
  - Benton, Eric & Simpson, Patricia CSSM/ CSJE 288A (Box 31, Folder 1588)
  - Lurie, Raymond CSSM/ CSBR 287b (Box 31, Folder 1589)
  - Ezra Stiles: Budgets & Costs 1986 (Box 31, Folder 1590)
  - Segal, Edward CSES/ CSSM 290A (Box 31, Folder 1591)
  - Adolphe, Bruce CSES/ CSSY 288A (Box 31, Folder 1592)
  - Adolphe, Bruce CSES/ CSPC 274A (Box 31, Folder 1593)
  - Rita Brackman CSES 291A (Box 31, Folder 1594)
  - Brackman CSTC/ CSBR 210A 1981 (Box 31, Folder 1595)
  - Trumbull College: Budgets & Costs 1986 (Box 31, Folder 1596)
  - Faulkner, Donald 1981, 1984, 1985, 1986 (five files bound together) (Box 31, Folder 1597)
  - Hyer, Brian CSTC/ CSTD 294b1986 (Box 32, Folder 1598)
  - Levine, Gilbert CSTC 290A 1985 (Box 32, Folder 1599)
  - Levine CSCC/ CSPC 101A (Box 32, Folder 1600)
  - Levine CSPC/ CSTD 75b (Box 32, Folder 1601)
  - Bloom, Harold CSES 293b1986 (Box 32, Folder 1602)
  - Bloom CSES 239b1983 (Box 32, Folder 1603)
  - Bloom CSES 228A 1982 (Box 32, Folder 1604)
  - Bloom CSES 208A 1981 (Box 32, Folder 1605)
  - Bloom CSES 136A 1978/ CSES 155A 1979 (Box 32, Folder 1606)
  - Jackson, Robert L. CSES 299b1986 (Box 32, Folder 1607)
  - Sander, Whitney CSES/ CSPC 298b1986 (Box 32, Folder 1608)
  - Greene, Julia CSSM/ CSJE 294b1986 (Box 32, Folder 1609)
  - Edelson, Marshall CSSM/ CSCC 301b1986 (Box 32, Folder 1611)
  - Marshall Edelson CSDC/ CSPC 270A 1984 (Box 32, Folder 1612)
  - Meyer, Esta Da Costa CSSM/ CSTC 297b1986 (Box 32, Folder 1613)
  - Lin & Rentoul CSSY/ CSBK 295b1986 (Box 32, Folder 1614)
  - Chin, Ann-Ping CSSY/ CSTC 297b1986 (Box 32, Folder 1615)
  - Savitt, Mark A. CSSY/ CSMC 299b1986 (Box 32, Folder 1616)
  - Stevens, Jose A. CSSY/ CSBK 298b1986 (Box 32, Folder 1617)
  - Gralla, Howard CSPC 291b1986 (Box 32, Folder 1618)
  - Howard Gralla CSPC 257b1984 (Box 32, Folder 1619)
  - Gralla CSPC 219b (Box 32, Folder 1620)
  - Gralla CSPC 191b1981 (Box 32, Folder 1621)
  - Gralla CSPC 144b (Box 32, Folder 1622)
  - Gralla CSPC 119b (Box 32, Folder 1623)
  - Munson, Russell CSPC 289A 1985 (Box 32, Folder 1624)
  - Russell W. Munson Jr. CSPC 271A 1984 (Box 32, Folder 1625)
  - Stewart, Richard CSPC/ CSCC 299b1986 (Box 32, Folder 1626)
  - Amanat, Abbas CSMC/ CSDC 297b (Box 32, Folder 1627)
  - Frank, Dana CSMC/ CSDC 294b1986 (Box 32, Folder 1628)
  - Dana Frank CSTC/ CSPC 260b1984 (Box 32, Folder 1629)
  - CTRC Agendas & Minutes 1986-87 (Box 32, Folder 1630)
  - Royal Copier- User=s Manual (Box 32, Folder 1631)
  - CTRC File -desk reference set/ Minutes 1986- 1987 (Box 32, Folder 1632)
  - Berkeley College: Budgets & Costs 1987 (Box 32, Folder 1633)
  - Blank, Stephen CSBK/ CSSM 304A 1986 (Box 32, Folder 1634)
  - Seldner, Joseph 1986 (Box 32, Folder 1635)
  - Branford College: Expenses & Costs 1987 (Box 32, Folder 1636)
  - Kupperman, Wendy J. CSBR/ CSPC 304A 1986 (Box 32, Folder 1637)
  - Watts, Linda CSBR/ CSSY 306A (Box 32, Folder 1638)
  - Feischacker, Samuel CSBR/ CSTD 303A 1986 (Box 32, Folder 1639)
  - Calhoun College 1986- 1987 (Box 32, Folder 1640)
  - Burt, Robert A. CSCC 309A 1986 (Box 32, Folder 1641)
  - Davenport College: Budgets & Costs 1986- 1987 (Box 32, Folder 1642)
  - Turner, Stansfield CSDC/ CSCC 307A 1986 (Box 32, Folder 1643)
  - Timothy Dwight College: Budgets & Costs 1987 (Box 32, Folder 1644)
  - Thomas, Hugh CSTD/ CSBK 302A 1986 (Box 32, Folder 1645)
  - Jonathan Edwards College: Budgets & Costs 1986- 1987 (Box 32, Folder 1646)
  - Rankin & Nolan CSJE/ CSSM 305A 1986 (Box 32, Folder 1647)
  - Rankin & Nolan CSDC/ CSJE 287b1985 (Box 32, Folder 1648)
  - Morse College: Budgets & Costs 1986- 1987 (Box 32, Folder 1649)
  - Greene,f. Dennis CSMC/ CSTD 305A 1986 (Box 33, Folder 1650)
  - Greene, Dennis CSBK 286A 1985 (Box 33, Folder 1651)
  - Nall- Langdon, Beva CSMC/ CSTD 301A 1986 (Box 33, Folder 1652)
  - Nall- Langdon, Beva CSES 292A 1985 (Box 33, Folder 1653)
  - Pierson College: Budgets & Costs 1987 (Box 33, Folder 1654)
  - Hauptman, Ira CSMC/ CSSM 302A 1986 (Box 33, Folder 1655)
  - Hauptman CSBR 56b (Box 33, Folder 1656)
  - Geise, Gerald CSPC 290b1986 (Box 33, Folder 1657)
  - Geise CSPC 284b1985 (Box 33, Folder 1658)
  - Thompson, Robert CSPC/ CSTC 305A 1986 (Box 33, Folder 1659)
  - Frum, David CSPC/ BR 302A 1986 (Box 33, Folder 1660)
  - Saybrook College: Expenses & Costs 1986- 1987 (Box 33, Folder 1661)
  - Frank, Julia CSSy 303A 1986 (Box 33, Folder 1662)
  - Julia Bess Frank CSSY/ CSJE 275A 1984 (Box 33, Folder 1663)
  - Moynihan, Ruth b. CSSY/ CSBK 303A 1986 (Box 33, Folder 1664)
  - Moynihan CSDC 206A 1981 (Box 33, Folder 1665)
  - Moynihan CSSM/ CSBR 187A 1980 (Box 33, Folder 1666)
  - Reeve, Franklin CSSY 302A 1986 (Box 33, Folder 1667)
  - Reeve CSSY 285b1985 (Box 33, Folder 1668)
  - CSSY/ CSMC 235bReeve 1983 (Box 33, Folder 1669)
  - Reeve CSSY 166b (Box 33, Folder 1670)
  - Reeve CSSY 59b (Box 33, Folder 1671)
  - Reeve CSSY 86b (Box 33, Folder 1672)
  - Reeve CSSY 132A (Box 33, Folder 1673)
  - Pierson, Paul CSSY/ CSBR 305A 1986 (Box 33, Folder 1674)
  - Clement, Constance CSSY/ CSBR 301A 1986 (Box 33, Folder 1675)
  - Clement, Constance CSSY/ CSBR 276A 1984 (Box 33, Folder 1676)
  - Silliman College: Budgets & Costs 1986- 1987 (Box 33, Folder 1677)
  - Ezra Stiles: Budgets & Costs 1986- 1987 (Box 33, Folder 1678)
  - McCourt, James CSES 301A 1986 (Box 33, Folder 1679)
  - Bewell, Alan CSES 304A 1986 (Box 33, Folder 1680)
  - Brodsky, Joseph CSES 303A 1986 (Box 33, Folder 1681)
  - Trumbull College: Expenses & Costs 1986- 1987 (Box 33, Folder 1682)
  - Hirschmann, Nancy J. CSTC 303A 1986 (Box 33, Folder 1683)
  - Hirschel, Anthony CSTC/ CSES 306b1987 (Box 33, Folder 1684)
  - Levy, Jim CSTC/ CSDC 1987 (Box 33, Folder 1685)
  - Gordon, Joseph CSSM/ CSPC 312b1987 (Box 33, Folder 1686)
  - Stacey, Robin CSSM/ CSTD 308b (Box 33, Folder 1687)
  - Robin Chapman Stacey CSTD/ CSSS 258b1984 (Box 33, Folder 1688)
  - Stacey CSTD/ CSES 235b1983 (Box 33, Folder 1689)
  - Halpern, Micah CSSM CSDC 310b1987 (Box 33, Folder 1690)
  - Bennett, Frances CSSM/ CSSY 314b1987 (Box 33, Folder 1691)
  - Kapilow, Ribert CSSM/ CSTD 307b1987 (Box 33, Folder 1692)
  - Marino, Carmen CSSY/ CSTC 309b1987 (Box 33, Folder 1693)
  - Marino, Carman CSMC/ CSBK 293b1986 (Box 33, Folder 1694)
  - M. Victoria Guerin CSSY/ CSSM 313b1987 (Box 33, Folder 1695)
  - Nkondo, Moses CSMC/ CSJE 307b1987 (Box 33, Folder 1696)
  - Cooke, Hope CSMC/ CSDC 309b1987 (Box 33, Folder 1697)
  - Hauf, Kandice CSPC/ CSSY 310b1987 (Box 33, Folder 1698)
  - Hauf, Kandice CSMC/ CSDC 286A (Box 33, Folder 1699)
  - Musser, Charles CSPC/ CSES 308b1987 (Box 33, Folder 1700)
  - Schiffer, Edward CSPC 306b1987 (Box 33, Folder 1701)
  - Rose, Elihu CSTD/ CSBK 310b1987 (Box 34, Folder 1702)
  - Rose CSTD/ CSMC 243b1983 (Box 34, Folder 1703)
  - Rose CSTD/ CSMC 194b1981 (Box 34, Folder 1704)
  - Rose CSTD 167b (Box 34, Folder 1705)
  - Lichtenstein, Alexander CSTD/ CSCC 311b1987 (Box 34, Folder 1706)
  - Trumpler, Maria CSTD/ CSPC 313b1987 (two folders bound) (Box 34, Folder 1707)
  - Wilson, Nancy CSJE 310b1987 (Box 34, Folder 1708)
  - Sullivan, Paul CSJE 309b1987 (Box 34, Folder 1709)
  - Shumway, Floyd CSDC/ CSTC 311b1987, 1986, 1983 (three folders) (Box 34, Folder 1710)
  - Bucki, Cecelia CSBR/ CSMC 312b1987 (Box 34, Folder 1711)
  - Lowry, Richard CSBR/ CSBK 311b1987 (Box 34, Folder 1712)
  - Hersh, Jeff CSBR/ CSSY 1987, 1986, 1985 (three folders bound) (Box 34, Folder 1713)
  - Goldstein, Daniel CSCC 313b1987 (Box 34, Folder 1714)
  - Brewer, Scott CSBK/ CSPC 307b1987 (Box 34, Folder 1715)
  - Ochs, Vanessa CSBK/ CSSM 309b1987 (Box 34, Folder 1716)
  - Svoboda, Charles CSBK CSDC 308b (Box 34, Folder 1717)
  - Stokes, Allison CSBK 312b1987 (Box 34, Folder 1718)
  - Fall 1987 Seminar Booklet (Box 34, Folder 1719)
  - Instructors' I-9's (Box 34, Folder 1720)
  - Instructors' I-9's (Box 34, Folder 1721)
  - Accounting Transfers-- Course Information (Box 34, Folder 1722)
  - Budget Information and Accounting Transfers (Box 34, Folder 1723)
  - Minutes & Agenda Fall 1987, Spring 1988 (Box 34, Folder 1724)
  - Enrollment Statistics Fall 1987 (Box 34, Folder 1725)
  - Appointments-- Spring 1988 (Box 34, Folder 1726)
  - Letters of Appointment & Release Time (Box 34, Folder 1727)
  - Letters of Appointment (before Fall 1986) (Box 34, Folder 1728)
  - Letters of Appointment (before Fall 1986) (Box 34, Folder 1729)
  - Articles Re: Coll Semfrey (Box 34, Folder 1730)
  - Correspondence: Spring 1988 (Box 34, Folder 1731)
  - Bursary Students (Box 34, Folder 1732)
  - Suggestions For Changes in Seminar Selection (Box 34, Folder 1733)
  - Skinner Report (Box 34, Folder 1734)
  - Letters of Appointment (before Fall 1986) (Box 34, Folder 1735)
  - New Telephone System (Box 34, Folder 1736)
  - Accounting Transfers 1987- 1988 (Box 34, Folder 1737)
  - Expense Reports 1988 (Box 34, Folder 1738)
  - Misc. Financial Forms 1987- 1988 (Box 34, Folder 1739)
  - Turekian, Karl CSBK 319A 1987 (three folders, bound) (Box 34, Folder 1740)
  - Matthews, Craig CSBK/ CSTD 317A 1987 (Box 34, Folder 1741)
  - Coppedge, Michael CSBK/ CSTC 318A 1987 (Box 34, Folder 1742)
  - Castiglia, Christopher CSBR/ CSMC 316A 1987 (Box 34, Folder 1743)
  - Keegan, John Fall 1987 (Box 35, Folder 1744)
  - Cole, Robert CSDC/ CSCC 318A 1987, 1986, 1984, 1983 (four folders) (Box 35, Folder 1745)
  - Buss, Sarah CSDC/ CSES 315A 1987 (Box 35, Folder 1746)
  - Pearson, David CSTD 318A 1987 (Box 35, Folder 1747)
  - Pearson CSTD 290b1986 (Box 35, Folder 1748)
  - James S. Davie CSTD 261b (Box 35, Folder 1749)
  - Davie & Pearson CSTD 237b1983 (Box 35, Folder 1750)
  - Davie CSTD 216b (Box 35, Folder 1751)
  - Davie & Pearson CSTD 168b (Box 35, Folder 1752)
  - Davie/ Pearson CSTD 142b (Box 35, Folder 1753)
  - Davie & Pearson CSTD 118b (Box 35, Folder 1754)
  - Davie/ Pearson CYTD 94b (Box 35, Folder 1755)
  - Wing, Marjorie CSJE 314A 1987 (Box 35, Folder 1756)
  - Herman, Kali CSSM/ CSMC 318A 1987 (Box 35, Folder 1757)
  - Wright, Alan CSMC/ CSBR 319A 1987 (Box 35, Folder 1758)
  - Culvahouse, Timothy CSMC/ CSBR 314A 1987 (Box 35, Folder 1759)
  - Cornell, John S. CSPC/ CSTD 315A (Box 35, Folder 1760)
  - Bradley, George CSSY 316A 1987 (Box 35, Folder 1761)
  - Ameling, Ann CSSY 317A 1987 (Box 35, Folder 1762)
  - Waley-Cohen, Joanna CSSY/ CSMC 315A 1987 (Box 35, Folder 1763)
  - Schirmeister, Pamela CSSM/ CSJE 316A 1987 (Box 35, Folder 1764)
  - Nolla, Eduardo CSES 320A 1987 (Box 35, Folder 1765)
  - Bruce, Marcus CSES/ CSJE 318A 1987 (Box 35, Folder 1766)
  - Linder, Mark CSTC/ CSJE 319A 1987 (Box 35, Folder 1767)
  - Isleib, Roberta CSTC 316A 1987 (Box 35, Folder 1768)
  - Maffly-Kipp, Laurie CSBK/ MC 321b1988 (Box 35, Folder 1769)
  - Brooks, Oliver CSBK 324b1988 (Box 35, Folder 1770)
  - Brooks, CSES 198b1981 (Box 35, Folder 1771)
  - Lesser, Rika CSBK/ CSJE 323b1988 (Box 35, Folder 1772)
  - Lesser, Rika CSES 309b1987 (Box 35, Folder 1773)
  - Brecher, Jeremy CSBR/ JE 321b1988 (Box 35, Folder 1774)
  - Stenzelm Conrad CSCC/ JE 325b1988 (Box 35, Folder 1775)
  - Hersenberg, Arvid CSCC 324b1988 (Box 35, Folder 1776)
  - Klein, Norma 1988, 1987 (two folders, bound) (Box 35, Folder 1777)
  - Stone, Forrest CSTC/ CSCC 310b1987 (Box 35, Folder 1778)
  - Stone CSDC 285b1985 (Box 35, Folder 1779)
  - Stone, Forrest CSSY/ CSDC 291A 1985 (Box 35, Folder 1780)
  - Stone, Forrest CSDC/ JE 327b1988 (Box 35, Folder 1781)
  - Trachtenberg, Zev CSDC/ TC 321b1988 (Box 35, Folder 1782)
  - Trachtenberg, Zev CSTC 296b/ CSBR 296b1986 (Box 35, Folder 1783)
  - Sherman, Joshua CSDC/ SY 322b1988 (Box 35, Folder 1784)
  - Sherman, Joshua CSJE 300A 1986 (Box 35, Folder 1785)
  - Sherman CSDC/ CSBK 279b1985 (Box 35, Folder 1786)
  - A. Joshua Sherman CSDC/ CSES 261b1984 (Box 35, Folder 1787)
  - Haltman, Kenneth CSTD/ MC 323 b1988, 1989 (two folders, bound) (Box 35, Folder 1788)
  - Spotts, Jules CSTD/ PC 326b1988 (Box 35, Folder 1789)
  - Favier, Dale CSTD/ BR 325b1988 (Box 35, Folder 1790)
  - Howell, Chris CSTD/ MC 322b1988 (Box 35, Folder 1791)
  - Kuryluk, Ewa CSJE/ CC 326b1988 (Box 35, Folder 1792)
  - Wright, Alan CSMC/ CSBR 308b1987 (Box 35, Folder 1793)
  - Wright, Alan 1986 (Box 35, Folder 1794)
  - Desmond, Jane CSPC/ BR 324b1988 (Box 35, Folder 1795)
  - Huginnie, Yvette CSSY/ MC 328b1988 (three folders, bound) (Box 36, Folder 1796)
  - Bloeminck, Barbara CSSY 321b1988 (Box 36, Folder 1797)
  - Main, Jeremy CSSY/ ES 325b1988 (Box 36, Folder 1798)
  - Phillippy, Patricia CSSM/ MC 325b1988 (Box 36, Folder 1799)
  - Conn, P. Jeffrey CSSM/ TC 324b1988 (Box 36, Folder 1800)
  - Lappin, Lou CSSM/ PC 328b1988 (Box 36, Folder 1801)
  - Cohen, Marc & Ratner, Jon CSSM/ PC 321b1988 (two folders) (Box 36, Folder 1802)
  - Nissenson, Hugh CSES 321b1986 (Box 36, Folder 1803)
  - Blood, Roger & Simpson, Patricia CSTC/ CC 326b1988 (Box 36, Folder 1804)
  - Instructors Info (Box 36, Folder 1805)
  - Instructors' I-9's 1989 (Box 36, Folder 1806)
  - Expense Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 1807)
  - Correspondence Fall 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1808)
  - Appointment Letters, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 1809)
  - CTRC Minutes 1988- 1989 (Box 36, Folder 1810)
  - Enrollment Statistics 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1811)
  - Appointment Letters 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1812)
  - Fischelis, Robert CSBK/ TD 337A 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1813)
  - Fischelis CSBK/ SM 365b1990 (Box 36, Folder 1814)
  - Sakvitne, Karen CSBK/ CSJE 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1815)
  - Badger, Anne CSBK/ CC 338A 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1816)
  - Badger, Anne CSTC/ CSCC 312b1987 (Box 36, Folder 1817)
  - Geyer, Tom CSBK 332A 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1818)
  - Geyer 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1819)
  - Pincus, Walter CSBR 331A 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1820)
  - Hanawa, Yukiko CSBR/ CSBK 333A (Box 36, Folder 1821)
  - French, Richard CSCC/ JE 337A 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1822)
  - Schaller, Barry CSBR/ CSES 332A 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1823)
  - Scaller, Barry CSCC/ CSBK 300b1986 (Box 36, Folder 1824)
  - Rubin 1989 (Box 36, Folder 1825)
  - Saussy, Hawn CSCC/ CSDC 333A 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1829)
  - Danilowitz, Brenda CSCC/ CSTC 332A 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1830)
  - Sheffer, Ethel CSDC/ CSCC 335A 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1831)
  - Halaban, Eytan 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1832)
  - Zonderman, Jon 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1833)
  - Altoschul, Charles CSPC/ CSSM 336A 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1834)
  - Guzzardi, Walter CSPC/ CSMC 333A 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1835)
  - Kunzel, Regina CSPC 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1836)
  - Kunzel, Regina CSPC/ CSES 316A 1987 (Box 36, Folder 1837)
  - Kunzel, Regina CSSM 1986 (Box 36, Folder 1838)
  - Barzalai, Gad CSSY/ CSES 2A 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1839)
  - Lawler, John CSES 335A 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1840)